{
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "this front side number 01",
      "back": "this is back side number 01",
      "char": "😀"
    },
    {
      "front": "this front side number 02",
      "back": "this is back side number 02",
      "char": "😌"
    },
    {
      "front": "this front side number 03",
      "back": "this is back side number 03",
      "char": "😍"
    },
    {
      "front": "this front side number 04",
      "back": "this is back side number 04",
      "char": "😎"
    },

    {
      "front": "this front side number 05",
      "back": "this is back side number 05",
      "char": "😷"
    },
    {
      "front": "this front side number 06",
      "back": "this is back side number 06",
      "char": "😸"
    },
    {
      "front": "this front side number 07",
      "back": "this is back side number 07",
      "char": "😹"
    },
    {
      "front": "this front side number 08",
      "back": "this is back side number 08",
      "char": "😺"
    },
    {
      "front": "this front side number 09",
      "back": "this is back side number 09",
      "char": "😻"
    },
    {
      "front": "this front side number 10",
      "back": "this is back side number 10",
      "char": "😼"
    },
    {
      "front": "this front side number 11",
      "back": "this is back side number 11",
      "char": "😽"
    },
    {
      "front": "this front side number 12",
      "back": "this is back side number 12",
      "char": "😾"
    },
    {
      "front": "this front side number 13",
      "back": "this is back side number 13",
      "char": "😿"
    },
    {
      "front": "this front side number 14",
      "back": "this is back side number 14",
      "char": "🙀"
    },
    {
      "front": "this front side number 15",
      "back": "this is back side number 15",
      "char": "🙁"
    },
    {
      "front": "this front side number 16",
      "back": "this is back side number 16",
      "char": "🙂"
    }
  ]
}